Omg
压制:随Feng
歌手:Usher
歌名:Omg  我的天
我的天啊
Oh my gosh
我再次播放最劲爆的节奏
Baby let me la..I did it again so Imma let the
天啊
Oh myyy
宝贝来让我宠坏你
Baby let me love you down
爱你有太多方法
There's so many ways to love ya
我也可以制服你
Baby I can break ya down
爱你有太多方法
There's so many ways to love ya
我已经爱的神魂颠倒
Got me like oh my god, i'm so in love
我最後找到了你 你让我想说
I found you finally, you make me want to say
我...已经爱的神魂颠倒
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh my gosh
你让我想说
You make want to say
Oh Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
我看上了那个美眉
I fell in love with shawty
当我在舞厅看到她
When I seen her on the dance floor
她性感轻盈的挑逗着舞动者
She was dancin' sexy, pop, pop, pop, and drop it and drop it low
绝没有谁像这样让我一见锺情
Never ever ever has a lady hit me on the first sight
她很特别
This was somethin' special
她充满活力
This was just like dynamite
她扭动着腰肢
Honey got a booty like, pow, pow, pow
她妖绕着身躯
Honey got some moves like wow oh wow
美眉你知道我迷恋着你这样型女
Girl you know i'm lovin your, your style
我已经认定了你
Check, check, check, checkin you out
她就是我的菜
She got it all
从头到脚的性感
Sexy from her head to toe
她让我迫不及待
And I want it all and all and all
宝贝来让我宠坏你吧
Baby let me love you down
爱你有太多方法
There's so many ways to love ya
我也可以制服你
Baby I can break ya down
爱你有太多方法
There's so many ways to love ya
我已经爱的神魂颠倒
Got me like oh my god, i'm so in love
我最後找到了你 你让我想说
I found you finally, you make me want to say
噢...我已经神魂颠倒
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh my gosh
你让我想说
You make want to say
Oh Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
满夜店的辣妹让我兴奋的发狂
Feel so for honey out of all the girls up in this club
这个给我 看一眼我就喜欢
This one got me whipped, just off one look, yep i fell in love
小妞你很特别 你充满活力
Girl you something special, you just like dynamite
你有没有注意到
You're you're you're you're you're you're you're out of sight
爱上你我神魂颠倒
Fell in love with honey like my, oh my
亲爱的你看起来既灵巧又聪明
Honey looking wonderful; fly, so fly
你像个超级模特
Honey like a supermodel; my, oh my
所以为什麼像个小孩一样沮丧呢
Baby how you do that, make a grown man cry
我已经认定了你
Ooh (oooh) baby, you got it alll
从头到脚的性感
Sexy from her head to the toes
我已经迫不及待
I want it all, it all, it all
宝贝来让我宠坏你吧
So, honey let me love you downnn
爱你有太多方法
There's so many ways to love ya
来让我制服你吧
Baby i can break it downnn
爱你有太多方法
There's so many ways to love ya
我已经爱的神魂颠倒 我最後找到了你
Got me like, ooh myy gosh i'm soo in love i found you finallyy
你让我想说
You make me want to say..
Oh Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
噢 我的天哪
Oh my gosh
Oh Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
噢 我的天哪
Oh my gosh
噢 我的
Oh my
噢 我的天哪
Oh myy gosh
我再次
I did it again
播放最劲爆的节奏
So i'm gone let the beat drop
噢 我的天哪
Oh oh oh myy
噢 我的
Oh oh oh my, my, my, my, my, my
噢 我的天哪
Ooh my gosh
压制:随Feng